            { "question": "What was Wolverine's original code name?", "answer": "Weapon X", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What group does 'Starlord' lead?", "answer": "Guardians of the Galaxy", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who was the older brother of Cyclops?", "answer": "Havoc", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is Black Widow's real name?", "answer": "Natasha Romanov", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Asgardian guards the Bifrost?", "answer": "Heimdal", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Ms. Marvel is part of what team?", "answer": "New Avengers", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the ancient mutant that created the 'Four Horseman' to serve him?", "answer": "Apocalypse", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the symbiotes greatest weakness?", "answer": "ultra-sonics", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the defender of Hell's Kichen", "answer": "Daredevil", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which double-agent did Hawkeye turn into a loyal S.H.E.I.L.D. operative?", "answer": "Black Widow", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Uncanny X-Men member has the power to teleport anywhere they can envision?", "answer": "Nightcrawler", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Avenger was the original magic-user of the team before Doctor Strange?", "answer": "Scarlet Witch", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which mutant inadvertently stopped the Secret Invasion with his cancerous cells?", "answer": "Deadpool", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What powerful superheroine's powers are light-based?", "answer": "Captain Marvel", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which diabolical demi-god is held at bay by the Sorcerer Supreme and the Outsiders?", "answer": "Dormammu", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is Wolverine's real name?", "answer": "James Logan", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who was the Green Goblin's successor?", "answer": "Hobgoblin", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which mercenary villian can copy any style of combat they see?", "answer": "Taskmaster", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is Beast's real name?", "answer": "Dr. Hank McCoy", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which web-slinger is actually a feral mutant clone of Peter Parker?", "answer": "Spider Doppleganger", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the name of the secret organization that infiltrated the ranks of S.H.E.I.L.D.? (acronym)", "answer": "H.Y.D.R.A.", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who does Venom blame for all his percieved misfortunes?", "answer": "Spiderman", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who became 'Agent Venom' in order to regain their ability to walk again?", "answer": "Flash Thompson", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who was the First Avenger?", "answer": "Captain America", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is Iron Man's real name?", "answer": "Tony Stark", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is Ant-man's partner?", "answer": "Wasp", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Doctor Doom is the arch-nemesis of which group of superheroes?", "answer": "Fantastic Four", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Marvel can see as well as manipulate light on any spectrum?", "answer": "Marvel Girl", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is The Thing's real name?", "answer": "Ben Grimm", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the Iron Man suit piloted by Colonel Brody called?", "answer": "War Machine", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What group includes the heroes of New York's various burroughs?", "answer": "Defenders", "asked": false },
            { "question": "The second Black Widow is part of what team?", "answer": "Thunderbolts", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the original Spiderman's real name?", "answer": "Peter Parker", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Outsider gained his powers from an infernal contract with Blackheart?", "answer": "Ghost Rider", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which former mentor of Peter Parker's became a supervillain when an accident permanently grafted robotic arms to his back?", "answer": "Doctor Octopus", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which web-slinger has unique psionic powers unlike any of the others?", "answer": "Spider-Woman", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Where is Blank Panther from?", "answer": "Wakanda", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the name of the intelligent plant-being on Starlords team?", "answer": "Groot", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the team leader of the Uncanny X-Men?", "answer": "Cyclops", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Uncanny X-Men member was able to produce blinding pyrotechnics from their hands?", "answer": "Jubilee", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Spiderman villain uses the powers of illusion and deception to mimic extraordinary powers?", "answer": "Mysterio", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which of the Defenders is the master of martial arts?", "answer": "Iron Fist", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Whose is the declared rival of the, 'Merc with the Mouth'?", "answer": "Wolverine", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who founded the X-Men Academy?", "answer": "Professor Charles Xavier", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the leader of the Inhumans?", "answer": "Black Bolt", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Guardian of the Galaxy lives only to avenge his dead family?", "answer": "Drax the Destroyer", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Uncanny X-Men has the ability to turn his skin into metal?", "answer": "Colossus", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who was Patriot before he took the place of Steve Rogers?", "answer": "Falcon", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the Dark Avenger Iron Man?", "answer": "Norman Osborn", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the First Avenger's real name?", "answer": "Steve Rogers", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Omega Red, Wolverine, Deadpool, and '        ' made up the original Weapon X team...", "answer": "Sabertooth", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Avenger is in possession of Mjolnir?", "answer": "Thor", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which flying mutant was turned into a Horseman by Apocalypse?", "answer": "Archangel", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which mutant is able to glide on waves of pure sound?", "answer": "Banshee", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which supervillain was only attempting to regrow his missing arm?", "answer": "The Lizard", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the prime directive of the Sentinel program?", "answer": "Neutralize all mutants", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Brotherhood mutant closely resembles a common amphibian?", "answer": "Toad", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Guardian of the Galaxy is a powerful empath?", "answer": "Mantis", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is Venom's real name?", "answer": "Eddie Brock", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which vigilante's deadly methods are considered too extreme for the Avengers?", "answer": "Punisher", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which of the original X-Men could literally freeze the air around themselves?", "answer": "Iceman", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Holocaust survivor created the satellite 'Asteroid M' as a sanctuary for mutants?", "answer": "Magneto", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which race colonized a significant portion of the known galaxy?", "answer": "Kree", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the brother of the Invisible Girl?", "answer": "The Human Torch", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who wouldn't you like to see get angry?", "answer": "Incredible Hulk", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Whose catchprase is, 'It's clobberin time!'", "answer": "The Thing", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is married to Mr. Fantastic?", "answer": "The Invisible Girl", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which member of the X-Men team suffers from debilitating claustrophobia?", "answer": "Storm", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which mutant underwent the adamantium skeletal bonding process in hopes of being able to finally kill Logan?", "answer": "Lady Deathstrike", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which former member of Weapon X possesses adamantium tentacles capable of draining his foes?", "answer": "Omega Red", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Marvel can convert light into matter?", "answer": "Ms. Marvel", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which race of shapeshifters nearly succeeded in their invasion of Earth?", "answer": "Skrull", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Avenger's homeland is the hidden source of vibranium on Earth?", "answer": "Black Panther", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which artificial being gains his god-like powers from an Infinity Stone?", "answer": "Vision", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which former antagonist became a valued headmistress of 'Xavier's School for Gifted Children'?", "answer": "Emma Frost", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which former gambler was once part of a secret cabal of killers?", "answer": "Gambit", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What was the Soviet Union's Iron Man called?", "answer": "Red Dynamo", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What primary force is the leadership of the Kree Empire?", "answer": "The Supreme Intelligence", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which intergalactic traveler was known as a 'herald of doom' for Galactus, the World-Eater?", "answer": "Silver Surfer", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which time-traveling mutant has the ability to absorb and channel energy?", "answer": "Bishop", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which meta did the Venom symbiote allegedly fail to bond with due to their incurable insanity?", "answer": "Deadpool", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which supervillian killed Mary Jane Watson?", "answer": "Green Goblin", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Where is the hidden city of the Inhumans located?", "answer": "Earth's Moon", "asked": false },
            { "question": "The tropical region buried near the Earth's core is called?", "answer": "The Savage Lands", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What is the name of Black Bolt's betrothed?", "answer": "Medusa", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which inter-dimensional being guides Peter Parker across the multi-verse?", "answer": "Madame Web", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What organization is Nick Fury the director of? (acronym)", "answer": "S.H.E.I.L.D.", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is Magneto's son?", "answer": "Quicksilver", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Outsider is known as the 'day-walker'?", "answer": "Blade", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which supervillain is in control of the Ten Rings?", "answer": "The Mandarin", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Outsider is also the Sorcerer Supreme?", "answer": "Doctor Strange", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which god was 'tricked' into believing he was Asgardian?", "answer": "Loki", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the Winter Soldier?", "answer": "Bucky Barnes", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who secretly is Nightcrawler's mother?", "answer": "Mystique", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the Dark Phoenix?", "answer": "Jean Grey", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which race of beings is actually a hybrid of humans and kree biology?", "answer": "The Inhumans", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Skrulls bio-engineered with powers to mimic certain meta-humans are called what?", "answer": "Super Skrull", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the 'Mad Titan'?", "answer": "Thanos", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which Guardian of the Galaxy most resembles a 'trash bandit'?", "answer": "Rocket", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What artificial intelligence did Tony Stark create only to have turn against him?", "answer": "Ultron", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which unstoppable supervillain is not actually a mutant?", "answer": "Juggernaut", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which of the Defenders is nearly indestructable?", "answer": "Luke Cage", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which X-Men member drains the powers of others by contact?", "answer": "Rogue", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who is the Dark Avenger Hawkeye?", "answer": "Bullseye", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Whose catchprase was, 'Excelsior!'? (hint: the immortal...", "answer": "Stan Lee", "asked": false },
            { "question": "What villain is in control of The Savage Lands?", "answer": "Mr. Sinister", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which symbiote calls Venom his progenitor?", "answer": "Carnage", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who has a suit powered by 'Pym' particles to change size?", "answer": "Ant-man", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who married Tony Stark?", "answer": "Pepper Potts", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who does Eddie Brock blame for all of his percieved misfortunes?", "answer": "Peter Parker", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who said, 'With great power comes great responsibility'?", "answer": "Ben Parker", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which villain of H.Y.D.R.A. was horribly disfigured in an attempt to create a super-soldier serum?", "answer": "Red Skull", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who helped Professor X create Cerebro?", "answer": "Magneto", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Which time-traveler is related to Cyclops?", "answer": "Cable", "asked": false },
            { "question": "How many Infinity Stones are there in total? (#)", "answer": "5", "asked": false },
            { "question": "Who does Thanos hope to appease by collecting all of the Infinity Stones to wipe out half the universe?", "answer": "Death", "asked": false },
